<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>Contents of tagpackprovider csh</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>tx_tagpackprovider_selections</csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:dataquery/locallang_csh_txtagpackproviderselections.xml</fileId>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index=".alttitle">Tag Pack selections</label>
			<label index=".description">Tag Pack selections provide a list of primary keys from one or more tables, from records corresponding to selected tags.</label>
			<label index="details">
				Tag Pack selections act as a secondary provider in a Tesseract structure.
			</label>
			<label index="name.alttitle">Name</label>
			<label index="name.description">Some significant name or label for the selection.</label>
			<label index="tables.alttitle">List of tables</label>
			<label index="tables.description">Select which tables to get the records from.</label>
			<label index="tags.alttitle">Tags selector</label>
			<label index="tags.description">Simply select some tags from the available ones to form a selection. Overrides tag selection from expressions (below).</label>
			<label index="tag_expressions.alttitle">Tags from expressions</label>
			<label index="tag_expressions.description">Use expressions to select tags instead of the above selector.</label>
			<label index="tag_expressions.syntax">
				Enter an expression on each line to select tags. Expressions are of the form:

				key: value

				Refer to the Expressions manual for more details about using expressions. Lines can be commented out with "#" or "//".
			</label>
			<label index="tag_expressions.details">
				Selection by expression will be overridden by manual selections made in the "Tags" field.
			</label>
			<label index="tags_override.description">When this box is checked, the tags fecthed using expressions will override the manually selected ones. Otherwise tags from both sources are merged.</label>
			<label index="logical_operator.alttitle">Logical operator</label>
			<label index="logical_operator.description">Choose "AND" to find items that match ALL tags. Choose "OR" (default) to find items that match any one tag.</label>
			<label index="logical_operator.details">
				Be warned that choosing the "AND" operator requires additional processing. This is due to the fact that the condition cannot be resolved in a singe database query. Instead some post-processing is needed, to find items that match all selected tags.
			</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>
